[
  { "question": "(10 + 2) - 5", "answer": 7, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "20 - (5 + 5)", "answer": 10, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(8 - 3) + 10", "answer": 15, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "15 + (10 - 2)", "answer": 23, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(6 + 6) - 2", "answer": 10, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "25 - (10 + 5)", "answer": 10, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(50 - 20) + 5", "answer": 35, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "100 - (30 + 20)", "answer": 50, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(12 + 8) - 10", "answer": 10, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "40 - (10 + 10)", "answer": 20, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(5 + 5) - 10", "answer": 0, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "1 + (6 - 4)", "answer": 3, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(5 + 7) - 2", "answer": 10, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(2 + 16) - 1", "answer": 17, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(19 + 2) - 5", "answer": 16, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "10 + (3 - 3)", "answer": 10, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(18 + 19) - 1", "answer": 36, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "4 + (7 - 5)", "answer": 6, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "16 + (4 - 9)", "answer": 11, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(18 + 8) - 4", "answer": 22, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(12 + 20) - 1", "answer": 31, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "2 + (7 - 3)", "answer": 6, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "18 + (9 - 6)", "answer": 21, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "15 + (3 - 1)", "answer": 17, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "5 + (4 - 4)", "answer": 5, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(2 + 6) - 5", "answer": 3, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "12 + (9 - 2)", "answer": 19, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "3 + (10 - 3)", "answer": 10, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(13 + 2) - 9", "answer": 6, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "14 + (4 - 6)", "answer": 12, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "6 + (2 - 7)", "answer": 1, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "5 + (4 - 3)", "answer": 6, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(15 + 10) - 3", "answer": 22, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "12 + (9 - 1)", "answer": 20, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(6 + 9) - 3", "answer": 12, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "16 + (1 - 6)", "answer": 11, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "10 + (9 - 10)", "answer": 9, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(5 + 8) - 8", "answer": 5, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(17 + 7) - 1", "answer": 23, "difficulty": 1 },
  { "question": "(15 + 9) - 2", "answer": 22, "difficulty": 1 },
  
  { "question": "[(5 + 5) - 2] + 10", "answer": 18, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "20 - [10 - (3 + 2)]", "answer": 15, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[15 + (5 - 2)] - 10", "answer": 8, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "50 - [(10 + 10) - 5]", "answer": 35, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[8 + (2 + 5)] - 5", "answer": 10, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "100 - [50 - (10 + 10)]", "answer": 70, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[20 - (5 + 5)] + 10", "answer": 20, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "30 - [(8 - 2) + 4]", "answer": 20, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[(12 + 8) - 10] + 5", "answer": 15, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "25 - [5 + (10 - 5)]", "answer": 15, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[6 - (3 + 4)] + 8", "answer": 7, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[4 - (4 + 1)] + 1", "answer": 0, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[9 - (1 + 5)] + 9", "answer": 12, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[13 - (1 + 5)] + 6", "answer": 13, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[29 - (4 + 3)] + 6", "answer": 28, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[14 - (5 + 1)] + 3", "answer": 11, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[24 - (10 + 4)] + 2", "answer": 12, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[25 - (7 + 3)] + 8", "answer": 23, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[19 - (9 + 1)] + 2", "answer": 11, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[11 - (8 + 1)] + 7", "answer": 9, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[16 - (3 + 2)] + 9", "answer": 20, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[20 - (3 + 3)] + 2", "answer": 16, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[30 - (9 + 3)] + 3", "answer": 21, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[30 - (8 + 1)] + 3", "answer": 24, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[6 - (4 + 1)] + 4", "answer": 5, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[18 - (9 + 1)] + 5", "answer": 13, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[7 - (10 + 1)] + 5", "answer": 1, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[3 - (6 + 1)] + 6", "answer": 2, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[27 - (4 + 3)] + 5", "answer": 25, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[8 - (6 + 1)] + 1", "answer": 2, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[6 - (7 + 2)] + 4", "answer": 1, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[15 - (2 + 3)] + 7", "answer": 17, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[27 - (6 + 5)] + 1", "answer": 17, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[8 - (10 + 4)] + 7", "answer": 1, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[22 - (7 + 5)] + 7", "answer": 17, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[9 - (4 + 4)] + 10", "answer": 11, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[17 - (7 + 1)] + 5", "answer": 14, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[26 - (10 + 2)] + 4", "answer": 18, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[27 - (10 + 3)] + 9", "answer": 23, "difficulty": 2 },
  { "question": "[29 - (1 + 4)] + 1", "answer": 25, "difficulty": 2 },
  
  { "question": "2 x [(3 + 2) - 1]", "answer": 8, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "[5 x (2 + 2)] - 10", "answer": 10, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "3 x [10 - (2 x 3)]", "answer": 12, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "[(4 x 5) - 10] x 2", "answer": 20, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "10 + [2 x (5 + 5)]", "answer": 30, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "[20 - (3 x 4)] x 5", "answer": 40, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "50 - [2 x (10 + 5)]", "answer": 20, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "4 x [(8 - 3) + 2]", "answer": 28, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "[10 + (5 x 2)] - 5", "answer": 15, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "100 - [10 x (2 + 3)]", "answer": 50, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "5 x [(2 + 9) - 5]", "answer": 30, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "2 x [(7 + 6) - 5]", "answer": 16, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "1 x [(10 + 7) - 4]", "answer": 13, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "4 x [(4 + 10) - 1]", "answer": 52, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "5 x [(5 + 1) - 1]", "answer": 25, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "3 x [(10 + 7) - 3]", "answer": 42, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "4 x [(2 + 3) - 3]", "answer": 8, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "1 x [(8 + 6) - 2]", "answer": 12, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "1 x [(5 + 1) - 2]", "answer": 4, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "5 x [(7 + 3) - 2]", "answer": 40, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "4 x [(3 + 7) - 4]", "answer": 24, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "4 x [(3 + 2) - 3]", "answer": 8, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "2 x [(6 + 7) - 3]", "answer": 20, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "3 x [(3 + 3) - 1]", "answer": 15, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "3 x [(7 + 3) - 1]", "answer": 27, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "5 x [(9 + 9) - 5]", "answer": 65, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "1 x [(9 + 7) - 1]", "answer": 15, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "4 x [(7 + 3) - 3]", "answer": 28, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "5 x [(5 + 1) - 4]", "answer": 10, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "3 x [(2 + 10) - 4]", "answer": 24, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "3 x [(10 + 6) - 1]", "answer": 45, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "3 x [(10 + 4) - 2]", "answer": 36, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "3 x [(8 + 7) - 3]", "answer": 36, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "3 x [(1 + 7) - 1]", "answer": 21, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "5 x [(3 + 4) - 1]", "answer": 30, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "2 x [(10 + 3) - 3]", "answer": 20, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "5 x [(4 + 5) - 1]", "answer": 40, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "2 x [(3 + 5) - 2]", "answer": 12, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "2 x [(3 + 4) - 3]", "answer": 8, "difficulty": 3 },
  { "question": "3 x [(3 + 3) - 4]", "answer": 6, "difficulty": 3 },

  { "question": "{ 2 x [ 5 + (3 x 2) ] } - 10", "answer": 12, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "100 - { 2 x [ 10 + (5 x 4) ] }", "answer": 40, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ [ (10 - 2) x 2 ] + 4 } - 10", "answer": 10, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "50 + { 3 x [ 20 - (4 x 2) ] }", "answer": 86, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 10 x [ (5 + 5) - 2 ] } - 50", "answer": 30, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "20 + { 5 x [ 6 - (2 x 2) ] }", "answer": 30, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ [ 8 x (2 + 1) ] - 4 } x 2", "answer": 40, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "10 + { 2 x [ (10 x 2) - 5 ] }", "answer": 40, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 5 + [ 3 x (10 - 6) ] } x 2", "answer": 34, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "60 - { 2 x [ 5 + (2 x 5) ] }", "answer": 30, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 3 x [ 2 + (2 x 1) ] } - 6", "answer": 6, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 4 x [ 9 + (5 x 2) ] } - 10", "answer": 66, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 2 x [ 2 + (2 x 4) ] } - 7", "answer": 13, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 2 x [ 8 + (5 x 1) ] } - 3", "answer": 23, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 3 x [ 6 + (1 x 3) ] } - 4", "answer": 23, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 4 x [ 7 + (4 x 3) ] } - 8", "answer": 68, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 4 x [ 1 + (5 x 4) ] } - 1", "answer": 83, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 4 x [ 10 + (2 x 1) ] } - 14", "answer": 34, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 3 x [ 7 + (3 x 1) ] } - 11", "answer": 19, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 1 x [ 6 + (1 x 4) ] } - 5", "answer": 5, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 4 x [ 5 + (1 x 1) ] } - 12", "answer": 12, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 1 x [ 7 + (4 x 3) ] } - 7", "answer": 12, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 3 x [ 4 + (3 x 4) ] } - 19", "answer": 29, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 4 x [ 4 + (1 x 4) ] } - 16", "answer": 16, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 4 x [ 6 + (3 x 1) ] } - 6", "answer": 30, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 2 x [ 10 + (5 x 2) ] } - 9", "answer": 31, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 3 x [ 10 + (3 x 3) ] } - 13", "answer": 44, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 1 x [ 2 + (3 x 4) ] } - 7", "answer": 7, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 4 x [ 2 + (3 x 1) ] } - 15", "answer": 5, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 3 x [ 10 + (3 x 3) ] } - 7", "answer": 50, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 3 x [ 2 + (4 x 2) ] } - 4", "answer": 26, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 2 x [ 5 + (1 x 4) ] } - 5", "answer": 13, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 1 x [ 5 + (5 x 4) ] } - 1", "answer": 24, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 3 x [ 4 + (4 x 2) ] } - 14", "answer": 22, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 3 x [ 6 + (3 x 3) ] } - 1", "answer": 44, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 4 x [ 6 + (5 x 1) ] } - 7", "answer": 37, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 3 x [ 7 + (1 x 4) ] } - 8", "answer": 25, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 4 x [ 6 + (2 x 4) ] } - 20", "answer": 36, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 1 x [ 9 + (3 x 3) ] } - 17", "answer": 1, "difficulty": 4 },
  { "question": "{ 3 x [ 7 + (5 x 3) ] } - 5", "answer": 61, "difficulty": 4 },
  
  { "question": "{ 20 / [ 2 + (6 / 2) ] } x 5", "answer": 20, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "100 / { 2 x [ 15 - (5 x 2) ] }", "answer": 10, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (20 - 4) / 4 ] + 5 } x 3", "answer": 27, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "50 - { 10 x [ 8 / (2 + 2) ] }", "answer": 30, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ 24 / [ (3 x 2) - 2 ] } + 10", "answer": 16, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ 30 / (2 + 3) ] x 5 } - 10", "answer": 20, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "10 + { 40 / [ (10 / 2) + 3 ] }", "answer": 15, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ 60 / [ 10 + (2 x 5) ] } x 10", "answer": 30, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "80 / { 2 x [ (10 - 2) / 4 ] }", "answer": 20, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (50 / 5) + 10 ] / 4 } x 5", "answer": 25, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (20 / 2) + 8 ] x 3 } - 2", "answer": 52, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (18 / 3) + 5 ] x 3 } - 7", "answer": 26, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (6 / 1) + 5 ] x 2 } - 7", "answer": 15, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (8 / 4) + 4 ] x 3 } - 1", "answer": 17, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (30 / 3) + 3 ] x 4 } - 6", "answer": 46, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (16 / 2) + 2 ] x 2 } - 7", "answer": 13, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (12 / 2) + 5 ] x 3 } - 2", "answer": 31, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (6 / 1) + 4 ] x 4 } - 10", "answer": 30, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (8 / 2) + 8 ] x 4 } - 2", "answer": 46, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (8 / 4) + 4 ] x 3 } - 7", "answer": 11, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (24 / 3) + 2 ] x 3 } - 8", "answer": 22, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (30 / 3) + 2 ] x 2 } - 7", "answer": 17, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (24 / 4) + 10 ] x 2 } - 8", "answer": 24, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (12 / 3) + 7 ] x 3 } - 4", "answer": 29, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (24 / 3) + 3 ] x 2 } - 9", "answer": 13, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (24 / 4) + 5 ] x 2 } - 6", "answer": 16, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (40 / 4) + 4 ] x 3 } - 9", "answer": 33, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (6 / 3) + 10 ] x 4 } - 9", "answer": 39, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (40 / 4) + 1 ] x 3 } - 5", "answer": 28, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (32 / 4) + 4 ] x 3 } - 8", "answer": 28, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (50 / 5) + 6 ] x 3 } - 1", "answer": 47, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (2 / 1) + 3 ] x 3 } - 9", "answer": 6, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (12 / 2) + 10 ] x 4 } - 2", "answer": 62, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (8 / 4) + 4 ] x 3 } - 1", "answer": 17, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (4 / 1) + 9 ] x 2 } - 10", "answer": 16, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (6 / 3) + 9 ] x 4 } - 2", "answer": 42, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (4 / 2) + 10 ] x 2 } - 10", "answer": 14, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (30 / 5) + 5 ] x 2 } - 1", "answer": 21, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (2 / 1) + 1 ] x 4 } - 10", "answer": 2, "difficulty": 5 },
  { "question": "{ [ (8 / 2) + 4 ] x 3 } - 3", "answer": 21, "difficulty": 5 },
  
  { "question": "{ 100 / [ (5 x 2) + (10 x 0) ] } + 90", "answer": 100, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ 144 / 12 ] + [ 5 x (2 + 2) ] } - 12", "answer": 20, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "200 - { 10 x [ (20 / 2) + (3 x 2) ] }", "answer": 40, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ 50 + [ 10 x (10 / 2) ] } / 2", "answer": 50, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (81 / 9) x 3 ] - 7 } + 20", "answer": 40, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "5 x { [ 30 / (2 + 1) ] + (10 - 2) }", "answer": 90, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ 4 x [ (100 / 10) + 5 ] } - 10", "answer": 50, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ 60 / (15 - 5) ] x 10 } + 40", "answer": 100, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ 120 / [ 2 x (3 + 3) ] } x 5", "answer": 50, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "10 + { [ (50 / 2) + 5 ] / 3 } x 10", "answer": 110, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (18 / 2) x 4 ] - 7 } + 5", "answer": 34, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (4 / 2) x 3 ] - 1 } + 12", "answer": 17, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (18 / 2) x 4 ] - 4 } + 12", "answer": 44, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (24 / 3) x 3 ] - 9 } + 17", "answer": 32, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (10 / 2) x 5 ] - 6 } + 7", "answer": 26, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (14 / 2) x 6 ] - 9 } + 19", "answer": 52, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (12 / 2) x 6 ] - 1 } + 5", "answer": 40, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (25 / 5) x 5 ] - 7 } + 10", "answer": 28, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (18 / 3) x 6 ] - 5 } + 10", "answer": 41, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (20 / 4) x 4 ] - 1 } + 1", "answer": 20, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (4 / 4) x 6 ] - 1 } + 14", "answer": 19, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (32 / 4) x 2 ] - 5 } + 3", "answer": 14, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (36 / 6) x 5 ] - 3 } + 19", "answer": 46, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (54 / 6) x 2 ] - 7 } + 18", "answer": 29, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (10 / 5) x 6 ] - 5 } + 5", "answer": 12, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (21 / 3) x 5 ] - 7 } + 1", "answer": 29, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (42 / 6) x 4 ] - 1 } + 16", "answer": 43, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (35 / 5) x 5 ] - 5 } + 12", "answer": 42, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (2 / 2) x 5 ] - 3 } + 17", "answer": 19, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (9 / 3) x 6 ] - 4 } + 15", "answer": 29, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (9 / 3) x 4 ] - 10 } + 8", "answer": 10, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (20 / 5) x 4 ] - 1 } + 19", "answer": 34, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (42 / 6) x 6 ] - 8 } + 18", "answer": 52, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (18 / 3) x 3 ] - 4 } + 16", "answer": 30, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (42 / 6) x 4 ] - 1 } + 20", "answer": 47, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (48 / 6) x 4 ] - 6 } + 17", "answer": 43, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (40 / 4) x 4 ] - 7 } + 2", "answer": 35, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (6 / 6) x 3 ] - 4 } + 3", "answer": 2, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (10 / 2) x 6 ] - 6 } + 14", "answer": 38, "difficulty": 6 },
  { "question": "{ [ (18 / 3) x 2 ] - 1 } + 8", "answer": 19, "difficulty": 6 }
]